http://www.freedomworks.org/privacy-policy

http://appserver-a4b2c260-nginx-3cce674db6b4435398bddf172d355c5a/privacy-policy
Log In
Contribute
Get InformedAbout UsIssuesScorecardsGet InvolvedJoinLearnTake ActionResourcesContactFoundationPrivacy Policy
202.783.3870
About UsIssuesTake ActionScorecardsShowsJoinMoreAbout FreedomWorks
Don't Shrink Our Drinks
A Comparison of Republican and Democrat Platforms to FreedomWorks’ Position on Major Issues
President Trump’s Top 4 Accomplishments in 4 Years
Join the Fight for Freedom
Government goes to those who show up. FreedomWorks makes it easy to hold your elected officials accountable in our fully interactive Action Center.
See More Actions
Scorecards:
Hold Congress Accountable
Want to see how your legislators voted on key FreedomWorks issues? You can use our key vote scorecards to see how they measure up.
Find Your Legislator
FreedomWorks Originals provides you entertainment and education to help you better understand economics, the workings of government, and our insight into the most important debates facing our nation today. Watch and subscribe today!
Watch Now
Subscribe Now
Become a FreedomWorks Member
Email *
Zip Code *
Leave this field blank
Contact FreedomWorks
111 K Street NE
Privacy Policy
WATCH NOWThe Battle for Senate Heats Up in Georgia | Inside the StoryWatch Here
page
Privacy Policy
(Last Updated: August 13, 2012)
Policy Statement
FreedomWorks is dedicated to protecting the privacy of our online members and donors. We’ve developed these easy-to-understand Privacy Practices from guidelines established by leading privacy organizations, including eTrust.com and the Better Business Bureau.
Gathering and Usage of Information
FreedomWorks collects personal information from you on a voluntary basis and we don’t require it to obtain non-membership access to FreedomWorks.org. The types of personal information we collect may include your name, mailing address, email address, and phone number.
We do not sell your email address or phone number to any third parties. Some activities on FreedomWorks.org explicitly involve sharing your personal information with a third party, such as your elected officials. If you sign a petition or similar call to action that has the express purpose of sending emails or petitions to Congress, the media, or similar, we will share your personal information with the target of the call to action.
On some occasions, we will make our membership postal mailing list available to allied organizations for the purpose of sending direct mail.
Opt-Out
FreedomWorks maintains several opt-out and opt-in email lists, including our weekly newsletter and special state and issue updates. We give you control over these subscriptions and at any time you may “opt-out” and remove your e-mail address from our files. There is an “unsubscribe” process detailed at the bottom of every email, or you can contact us at http://www.freedomworks.org/contact to be removed from our email list.
Cookies
FreedomWorks.org uses “cookie” technology to obtain non-personal information from our online visitors, such as browser/computer type, number of visitors, IP address, and site usage. We don’t use cookies to extract personal information.
Links
Although FreedomWorks.org contains links to other sites, FreedomWorks does not necessarily advocate, support or condone the privacy practices or content of these various Web sites.
Public Forums
At FreedomWorks.org, you have the opportunity to participate in various online contests, comment boards, and discussions. Please remember that any information that you disclose in our chat rooms, forums, message boards, or new groups becomes public information. Exercise caution when deciding to disclose any of your personal information, and please do not disclose direct contact information such as your mailing address, phone number, or email address.
Security
FreedomWorks has taken steps to make all information received from our online visitors as secure as possible against unauthorized access and use. All information is protected by our security measures, which are periodically reviewed.
Ongoing Privacy Efforts
FreedomWorks approaches our Internet communications with respect for and commitment to individual privacy rights and concerns. We support active self-regulation of this environment to ensure that responsible organizations maintain the right to use all communications media to interact with the public. As the Internet evolves, our policy will continue to develop. Please check back periodically to see changes and additions.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about our privacy practices or the FreedomWorks Web Site, please contact us by calling (202) 783-3870 or contact us online.
In Action
Don't Shrink Our DrinksPut a cork in unscientific alcohol guidelines. Take action now!
LEARN MOREPresident Trump’s Top 4 Accomplishments in 4 YearsLEARN MOREA Comparison of Republican and Democrat Platforms to FreedomWorks’ Position on Major IssuesSave Our Country CoalitionFreedomWorks Foundation, American Legislative Exchange Council, Tea Party Patriots and Committee to Unleash Prosperity in partnership with a coalition of conservative organizations and prominent individuals, launched the Save Our Country Task Force.
LEARN MORE2020 Platform & Activist PledgeFreedomWorks is proud to roll out its 2020 policy platform for the Republican Party.
LEARN MOREStop the Socialist Green New DealHelp stop the Democrats’ socialist Green New Deal by signing the petition.
SIGN THE PETITION
Default Sidebar Signup Form
Want more freedom? Become a member today!
Your Email *
Zip *
Leave this field blank
Contribute
